<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://patters3dogs.github.io/blog</id>
    <title>patters3dogs Blog</title>
    <updated>2023-08-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://patters3dogs.github.io/blog"/>
    <subtitle>patters3dogs Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://patters3dogs.github.io/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I have learned on MLOps]]></title>
        <id>https://patters3dogs.github.io/blog/What-I-have-learned-on-MLOps</id>
        <link href="https://patters3dogs.github.io/blog/What-I-have-learned-on-MLOps"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi. For a while, I have learned about MLOPs in Coursera. It is very Interesting area of work, because it containing very thing that I need to known for increasing realiability for my own automate trading system.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi. For a while, I have learned about MLOPs in Coursera. It is very Interesting area of work, because it containing very thing that I need to known for increasing realiability for my own automate trading system. </p><p>MLOps is a set of Ideas for create Machine learning for production, which also contain DataOps, DevOps. In the past, for me, I created a Machine Learning model, and then move to my personal trading system without any mandatory approch, sometime it causes my app broken down. For now I can design more robustness application that can apply Machine Learning mode with a systemtic workflow.</p><p>In the course that I have been taken are mainly focused on cloud computing platform. Personally, I have lots of experience in AWS, however I still lag of ideas for creating a robust system for my retail trading system. </p><p>Here, These next blogs, I will shared my ideas and implementations of MLOps concept on my own retail automate trading system on AWS.</p><p>To be continue...</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>patters3dogs</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/patters3dogs</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="MLOps" term="MLOps"/>
        <category label="AWS" term="AWS"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings!]]></title>
        <id>https://patters3dogs.github.io/blog/greetings</id>
        <link href="https://patters3dogs.github.io/blog/greetings"/>
        <updated>2023-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, my name is Pattana Somroob. You can know me more on readme page of this site.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi, my name is Pattana Somroob. You can know me more on readme page of this site.</p><p>First, I appreciate to introduce my blog on patters3dogs.github.io. For me, sharing stuffs that I was learn is particularly important for my learning process. Just only reading and get course certificates is not sufficient for proficiency things, at least can recall what I learned are collect. This is an illusion of competence. To avoid this, I created this web blog to improve my learning outcome. To do so, I will write blogs or lecture notes for my learning process. In addition, I hope that my site will share my knowledge and contribute learning community.</p><p>My interesting fields of study are complex system science. This kind of science is wide range of knowledge that integrated of mathematics, engineering (multi-disciplinary), science and computation. In addition, I am also fascinated in simulation visualization and game development. Making a virtual life and computation simulation is remarkably interesting. Moreover, my personal curiosity is algorithmic trading.</p><p>Currently, I am working on software development. Therefore, I may share some IT tutorials on this web blog too.</p><p>Here, this is my first writting on the blogs, it is just a greeting. I hope that this site will have more contents soon.</p><p>See you next time :)</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>patters3dogs</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/patters3dogs</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="greetings" term="greetings"/>
    </entry>
</feed>