<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>patters3dogs Blog</title>
        <link>https://patters3dogs.github.io/blog</link>
        <description>patters3dogs Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Greetings!]]></title>
            <link>https://patters3dogs.github.io/blog/greetings</link>
            <guid>https://patters3dogs.github.io/blog/greetings</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hi, my name is Pattana Somroob. You can know me more on readme page of this site.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hi, my name is Pattana Somroob. You can know me more on readme page of this site.</p><p>First, I appreciate to introduce my blog on patters3dogs.github.io. For me, sharing stuffs that I was learn is particularly important for my learning process. Just only reading and get course certificates is not sufficient for proficiency things, at least can recall what I learned are collect. This is an illusion of competence. To avoid this, I created this web blog to improve my learning outcome. To do so, I will write a blog or lecture notes for my learning process. In addition, I hope that my site will share my knowledge and contribute learning community.</p><p>My interesting fields of study are complex system science. This kind of science is wide range of knowledge that integrated of mathematics, engineering (multi-disciplinary), science and computation. In addition, I am also fascinated in simulation visualization and game development. Making a virtual life and computation simulation is remarkably interesting. Moreover, my personal curiosity is algorithmic trading.</p><p>Currently, however, I am working on software development. Therefore, I may share IT tutorials stuffs on this site too.</p><p>Lastly, I my determination is write this blog more often as I can, for instance once a week, at least.</p><p>Here, this is my first writing on this site, it is just a greeting. I hope that this site will have more contents soon.</p><p>See you next time :)</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>greetings</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>